During the Sunday service at The SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua begins to move
in the midst of the congregation under the check and conduct of the Holy Spirit.
The results are clear - healing and deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ.
Amidst the crowd is this young lady who falls violently to the ground as she receives prayer.
The evil spirit that was lurking in her has been exposed by the power of God.
Let's watch what happens next.
So she's free from the spirit of man inside her.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Thank you, Jesus!
Testimony Time
My name is Lisa Venant, I'm twenty-three years old.
The woman standing beside me is my mother. I am from Tanzania.
Last Sunday the man of God delivered me from the spirit of man.
It has been tormenting me since I was 10 years old. I was in grade 3 by then.
It has lived inside me for 13 years.
This spirit got into me through dreams. I have been dreaming I was sleeping with a woman.
It has been living in me and whenever I used to wake up in the morning,
I used to have that desire of sleeping with a woman.
Any woman who used to come in front of me -
I used to approach any woman by that time I was in grade 3.
No woman ever denied me. They used to accept me.
It lived in me till I reached secondary school.
At that time I was in a boarding school.
Everything that I'm saying - my mum doesn't know about it.
When I was in secondary school, we had two preps - we had morning preps and night preps.
During morning preps, whenever they announced that we had to go to the classes to study,
I used to stay in the dormitory, sleeping with a woman.
Evening and morning preps I used to do the same.
At that time I used to sleep with three or four women per day.
So that spirit lived in me till I got to university.
I met one woman.
She approached me. I never knew she was married.
We dated and used to sleep together. We had a relationship.
I never knew till the husband called me and warned me to stay away from his wife.
I did that.
But at that instant, he called my mom.
I don't know how he got her number and he told my mom to warn me to stay away from his wife.
I remember that day my mom called me and asked me about it.
But I never accepted it and denied that it was true.
I used to dress like a man, talk like a man, behave like a man.
I used to have that desire of sleeping with women - any woman who would just pass by.
I had that spirit pushing me - whenever I saw a woman,
I could never just let her pass me by.
So I just found myself approaching them.
But since I've been delivered, I'm sleeping well. I don't have that desire for women anymore.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus!
Yes, sister, before you tell us how God Almighty delivered you from that spirit,
can you share with us: Did you have any experience in the past that you will never forget
while you were tormented by this demon who caused you to have a desire for women like you?
Yes, I remember there was a day...
I'm talking about the past. I dated one woman.
We went to a hotel and I never knew the receptionist called the police and they came into our room.
That was an instance I will never forget.
Have you ever made any attempt to stop on your own, since you knew that this was a spirit
that was tormenting you, that you could not control?
Did you try to stop it by yourself?
Yes.
I visited different churches seeking for my deliverance.
But because that spirit inside me was very strong -
the more I sought for deliverance, the more the spirit was pushing me
and taking me into that thing that has been tormenting me - the spirit of man.
And now, can you share with us: How did you finally come to The SCOAN?
After my mom realized that that spirit was tormenting me, she begged me to come to The SCOAN.
Because of that spirit, I used to deny it before.
But because of what I've been going through, how my life has been,
I decided to accept my mom's offer and I said: "Okay, mom, now it's time to go to The SCOAN
to seek for mercy and my deliverance."
Last week, as you saw on the television, the man of God touched me.
He delivered me from the spirit of man that had been tormenting me for 13 years.
Right now, I thank God I'm free and I give God the glory.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus once again.
I give God the glory. I never used to put on earrings in my life.
I never used to dress like a lady but now I can see changes in me.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus!
With what God Almighty has done for you - before we listen to your mother -
what advice can you give to the youth?
My friends, even my brothers and sisters who are in this church right now,
the advice that I want to give you:
Please, I beg. If you have the same spirit that was tormenting me, please seek God.
Talk to your parents.
Explain to them what you feel, what you always dream - the bad dreams that you always have
so that they can seek for help. This spirit is a very bad spirit. It confuses you.
You lose your career. You cannot focus. It was very hard on me.
So please, if you have this spirit, just talk to your parents,
seek for God's help and He will help you.
My parents, if you have your children at home...
As I said, this spirit was tormenting me for 10 years.
You might think your child is a little kid of 8, 9 or 10.
But that's the age when the devil is very close to the kids
and he's tormenting them with different spirits.
So please, try and look after your kids. Focus on them.
Especially those who are in boarding schools, because there is a different type of life there.
You meet different people, different characters.
So please, whenever they come on holiday, get close to your kid
and that will help you to know, if it has any problem that is tormenting him or her.
Once again, let us put our hands together for our Lord Jesus.
We give all the glory to God and we are very blessed by your advice.
We believe that viewers all around the world are listening to your advice -
parents are listening, guardians are listening.
I believe that the Lord will guide them to be able to look after their children
and train them in the way of the Lord, in Jesus' name.
My name is Flora Bina Moon.
I came from Tanzania. The lady beside me is my daughter.
The problem that brought us here to The SCOAN
was that spirit of man that was tormenting my daughter.
I thank God that last Sunday, she got her deliverance.
The other thing she has confessed here - I didn't know that for almost 13 years...
Until that man called me and told me that I should tell my daughter to stay away from his wife.
I was so confused; I was shocked.
I called my daughter and asked her; she denied it.
After one week, she called me and said, "Mom, I'm sorry.
That spirit has been tormenting me for a long time."
She started confessing to me.
After her deliverance, what are the changes that you have noticed as a mother?
I've seen a lot of changes - she sleeps well. Before, she didn't sleep.
At night, she used to chat on the phone - till the morning.
She walked like a man. She talked like a man.
But since last Sunday, she talks like a lady, she is close to me.
I thank God.
You said she would normally chat on her phone in the past.
Yes.
But now?
Now she's not chatting anymore.
With all you have heard from your daughter - what advice would you like to give to parents?
I advise all parents all over the world to watch and see what their kids are doing and seek God.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus!
Deliverance Testimony
Because of the language barrier, her mommy is giving advice to parents all around the world
to please look after their children.
Don't say your children must get to a certain age before you watch over them
but at a young age, like our sister said - age of 8-9 years
- even the age you wouldn't think you needed to watch your children -
so that satan will not take them away from you.
We believe that the same God who has restored our sister, that has delivered her
from the spirit of man, will also deliver those who were listening to her right now,
those who have a similar problem, in Jesus' name.
After her dramatic deliverance and inspiring testimony,
it is time for Lisa Vilant to return to her homeland of Tanzania.
Lisa is eager for the very first time in her life to actually wear female clothing.
Taken into a shop, she begins to choose and size up various items of female clothing -
something she had never done before in her life.
Truly, she has been returned to the original position in which God created her - a female.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua says:
"Faith is the transformative power of the universe - the power of change
from where you are, to where God wants you to be."
Lisa Venant & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
Beautifully dressed in a skirt and blouse.
Lisa Venant & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
Lisa is about to embark on her journey back to Tanzania with her mother.
Lisa Venant & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
A smile on her face says it all.
She is free indeed. And the spirit of man has gone forever.
Indeed, what a God we have to worship!
What a Son we have to praise and what a future lies before us!
Thank You, Jesus Christ!
TT: Jacqueline Margaret 17/12/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/12/2018 + Mel